&gt；&gt；Kyle：让我们看看调用函数的四种不同方式。
&gt;&gt; Kyle: So let's look at those four different ways to invoke a function.
我们将研究的第一个方法称为隐式绑定。
The first of them we'll look at is called implicit binding.
你会注意到我有一个工作坊对象，它上面有一个方法，就是这一点。
You'll notice I have a workshop object with a method on it that is this aware.
这对你来说应该很眼熟，因为我把它叫做
That should look familiar to you because I called that
我们讨论的另一个单元中的名称空间模式。
the name space pattern in another unit of our discussion.
我们在这里重新讨论命名空间模式
We're revisiting that name space pattern here and
我们将问一下this关键字在该命名空间模式中的行为？
we're gonna ask how does the this key word behave in that namespace pattern?
当我调用问题时，
When I get the ask question invoked,
它如何确定this关键字应该指向什么？
how does it figure out what the this keyword should point at?
答案是因为调用地点。
And the answer is because of the call site.
由于调用位置的原因，this关键字最终将指向该对象
Because of the call site, the this keyword is gonna end up pointing at the object
用于调用它的，在本例中第8行是工作坊对象。
that is used to invoke it, which in this case on line 8 is the workshop object.
ask表示调用ask，并将this关键字指向工作坊。
workshop.ask says invoke ask with the this keyword pointing at workshop.
这就是隐式绑定规则所说的。
That's what the implicit binding rule says.
顺便说一句，这对你来说应该是直观的，因为这就是
And by the way, that should be intuitive to you because that's exactly how
this绑定可以在其他语言中工作。
the this binding works in other languages.
所以这个特殊的规则是最常见和最直观的
So this particular rule is the most common and the most intuitive
因为它根据您从哪个函数调用它来决定方法，我的意思是，
because it decides the method based upon what function you call it from, I mean,
从哪个对象调用它。
what object you call it from.
但这只是四种方法中的一种，而且
But it's only one of the four ways, and
这就是额外的困惑可能出现的地方。
that's where the extra confusion can come in.
&gt；&gt；Kyle：顺便说一下，使用隐式绑定的想法很有用，因为
&gt;&gt; Kyle: By the way, the idea of having implicit binding is useful because
这就是我们如何在不同的上下文中共享行为。
this is how we share behavior among different contexts.
这里我只定义了一个Ask函数，但是
Here I am defining just one ask function, but
我在两个不同的对象之间共享ask函数。
I'm sharing the ask function across two different objects.
Workshop1和
workshop1 and
Workshop2，两个独立的对象，其中包含两个独立的数据片段。
workshop2, two separate objects with two separate pieces of data in them.
但因为在第7行和第12行，我在上面引用了ask函数。
But because on line 7 and line 12 I have a reference to the ask function on it.
当我使用该引用调用ask函数时，隐式
When I use that reference to invoke the ask function, the implicit
绑定规则说每次在不同的上下文中调用一个函数。
binding rule says invoke that one function in a different context each time.
所以我们没有两个Ask函数，只有一个，但是
So we don't have two ask functions there, just one, but
它在两个不同的上下文中调用。
it's invoked in two different contexts.
我可以做不止2次，但我可以做5次，
And I could do that not just 2 times, but I could do it 5 times,
或者1000次，或者100万次。
or 1,000 times, or 1 million times.
在许多不同的上下文中使用的一个函数。
One function used in lots of different contexts.
&gt；&gt；Kyle：如果你回想一下我们是如何描述词汇范围的概念的，
&gt;&gt; Kyle: If you think back to how we described the idea of lexical scope,
词法范围的概念是一个非常固定的、可预测的东西。
the idea of lexical scope is a very fixed, predictable thing.
它是在作者时定义的，关于运行时的任何东西都不能改变这一点。
It's defined at author time, and nothing about the run time can ever change that.
在这里，我们有一些不是固定的东西，
And here we have something which is not fixed and
可预测，它完全是动态的，完全在运行时确定。
predictable, it's entirely dynamic, it's entirely determined at run time.
这里的交易不是偶然的，这里的交易是非常有意的，
And the trade off here is not accidental, the trade off here is very intentional,
我们真正得到的是
that what we really are getting is we're getting
可预测和灵活之间的选择。
the choice between predictable and flexible.
在这里，我受益于能够共享一个功能的灵活性
Here I benefit from the flexibility of being able to share one function
跨越不同的背景。
across different contexts.
但有时这种灵活性是不利的
But there are times when that flexibility is a downside and
我更喜欢的是具有可预测性。
what I would prefer is to have predictability.
不是说一个是对的另一个是错的，
It's not that one is right and the other's wrong,
只是这些是不同的工具，它们有不同的好处。
it's just that these are different tools and they have different benefits.
在这里，我们看到了this关键字的灵活性优势。
Here we're seeing the flexibility benefit of the this keyword.
&gt；&gt；Kyle：还有另一种调用函数的方法，
&gt;&gt; Kyle: There's another way to invoke functions,
我们在几张幻灯片前看到了这个.call方法。
we saw this just a couple of slides ago, the .call method.
call方法及其表亲.dot apply方法，
The .call method along with it's cousin, .dot apply method,
它们都将this关键字作为第一个参数。
both of them take, as their first argument, a this keyword.
所以在第13行，当我们说.call并传入Workshop1时，
So on line 13, when we say .call and we pass in workshop1,
它是说调用带有workshop1的this上下文的ask函数。
it is saying invoke the ask function with the this context of workshop1.
它与上一张幻灯片非常相似，我们仍在共享该功能，
It's very similar to the previous slide, we are still sharing that function,
但现在我们这样做是明确的，而不是隐含的。
but now we're doing so explicitly rather than implicitly.
我们的意思是无论这个函数是从哪里来的，
We're saying wherever this function comes from,
在我将要指定的特定上下文中调用它。
invoke it in a particular context which I'm going to specify.
&gt；&gt；Kyle：所以我们可以使用.call和
&gt;&gt; Kyle: So we can use .call and
.application显式告诉JavaScript在哪个上下文中调用它。
.apply to explicitly tell JavaScript which context to invoke it in.
现在，我们将讨论显式绑定的一种变体，
Now, we're gonna talk about a variation of explicit binding,
这是我们正在研究的第二条规则。
this is the second of the rules that we're looking at.
但这不是一个单独的规则，而是一种子规则或
But this isn't a separate rule, but kind of a sub-rule or
此规则的子部分，这是一个非常常见的场景或
a sub-part of this rule, which is an extremely common scenario or
现象称为丢失您的此绑定。
phenomenon referred to as losing your this binding.
如果您曾经使用过传递的函数，并且
If you've ever worked with a function that you pass around, and
突然之间，它曾经有一个这样的绑定
all of a sudden, it used to have a this binding and
现在它没有这个绑定，你知道我在说什么。
now it doesn't have a this binding, you know what I'm talking about.
当你认为this关键字是可预测的，这是非常令人沮丧的
It's very frustrating when you think of a this keyword as being predictable and
然后你会发现，实际上，它是不可预测的，它是灵活的。
then you find out oops, actually, it's not predictable, it's flexible.
因此显式绑定的变体称为硬绑定。
So variation of explicit binding is called hard binding.
看一下第8行，如果我传入了workshop.ask，该方法
Looking at line 8, if I passed in workshop.ask, that method
在车间对象上，但第8行不是调用地点。
is on the workshop object, but that line 8 is not the call site.
你必须在脑海中想象一下，呼叫地点会是什么样子
You have to imagine in your head, what would the call site look like for
从现在开始计时器运行十毫秒时的函数？
the function whenever that timer ran ten milliseconds from now?
这个调用站点看起来像CB[]，或者类似的东西。
And that call site would look like cb[], or something like that.
它看起来不会像Workshop.ask，因为它看起来不像那样，
It's not going to look like workshop.ask, and because it doesn't look like that,
它不会在研讨会上下文中调用Ask。
it's not going to invoke ask in a workshop context.
这就是我们失去了我们的这个绑定，我们最终变得不确定。
Which is we've lost our this binding, we end up getting undefined.
实际上就像附注一样，从技术上讲，设置超时实用程序
Actually just as side note, technically, the set timeout utility
是由HTML定义的，它不仅仅是通过默认调用来唤起它，
is defined by HTML, it's not evoking it just with the default call,
它实际上在global上下文中使用.call显式调用它。
it actually explicitly invokes it with a .call in the context of global.
因此它实际上会通过说cb.call window来调用workshop.ask。
So it would actually invoke workshop.ask by saying cb.call window, essentially.
在全局对象上下文中调用它，对吗？
Invoking it in the global object context, yes?
&gt；&gt；Speaker 2：如果Ask为我们找到一个箭头函数，这是不是没有必要？
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Would this be unnecessary if ask were to find us an arrow function?
&gt；&gt；Kyle：在这里询问，因为箭头函数不能解决问题，但是
&gt;&gt; Kyle: Ask here as an arrow function would not solve the problem, but
我们一会儿就会讨论箭头函数，我们会回来的。
we are gonna talk about arrow functions in just a moment, so we'll come back that.
所以第8行，我们失去了这个绑定
So line 8, we're losing our this binding and
它实际上正在反弹到其他东西，在本例中是全局对象。
it's actually getting rebound to something else, in this case the global object.
这不是我们想要的。
That's not what we want.
因此，一个非常常见的解决方案是第11行，它传递一个硬绑定函数。
So a very common solution to this is line 11, passing a hard bound function.
如果我们使用.bind方法传入硬绑定函数，
If we pass in a hard bound function using the .bind method,
它会夺走整个灵活性
it will take away that whole flexibility thing and
强制它只使用我们在第11行指定的this。
force it to only use the this that we've specified on line 11.
它说唤起这个函数，无论你如何调用它，
It says evoke this function, and no matter how you invoke it,
始终使用研讨会，因为它是这样的上下文。
always use workshop as it's this context.
换句话说，.bind方法，它不调用函数，
In other words the .bind method, it doesn't invoke the function,
它产生一个新函数，该函数绑定到特定的this上下文。
it produces a new function which is bound to a particular specific this context.
所以你在这里看到了一个取舍，对吗？
So you see a trade-off here, right?
你看到的是可预测的，灵活的这种绑定，但随后你会看到一些
You see the predictable, flexible this binding, but then you see some
在这样的情况下，(听起来)它的灵活性有点令人沮丧。
scenarios where, [SOUND] it's kind of frustrating that it's flexible.
我真正想要的是它是超级可预测的。
And what I'd really like is for it to be super predictable.
这里有紧张气氛。
There's a tension here.
这并不是说一个是对的，另一个是错的。
It's not to say that one is right and the other is wrong.
但如果你不厌其烦地定义一些函数
But if you were to go to all the trouble to define a bunch of functions on some
命名空间对象，以及
namespace object, and
将这个点放在每个属性引用和每个方法访问的前面。
have this dot in front of every property reference and every method access.
然后所有的函数调用都使用.bind，
And then all of your function calls use the .bind,
你会割断自己的膝盖。
you would be cutting yourself off at the knees.
因为这个系统的整个目的，你纳税的整个原因
Because the whole purpose of this system, the whole reason that you pay the tax of
把这个点放在所有东西的前面就是为了获得动态性。
putting this dot in front of everything is to get the dynamicism.
然后你会把整个动力系统
And then you're going and taking that whole dynamic system and
锁定它所以它是完全可预测的。
locking it down so that it's completely predictable.
在这一点上，编写一个模块不是更好吗
At that point, wouldn't you be better served simply writing a module
使用闭包并且有固定的，可预测的行为？
that uses closure and has a fixed, predictable behavior?
那么我们如何处理这种紧张关系呢？
So how do we deal with this tension?
我们喜欢使用this关键字，它可能对我们很有用，但是
We like using the this keyword, it can be useful to us, but
有时我们需要它不那么灵活。
there are times when we need it to not be so flexible.
我不能为你解决这种紧张，但是
I can't solve that tension for you, but
我可以给你一种我使用的启发式。
I can just give you a sort of heuristic that I use.
如果我不厌其烦地编写一组可感知的代码，并且
If I go to the trouble to write a this aware set of code, and
然后我的大部分核心站点都在使用灵活的动态机制，
then most of my core sites are using the flexible dynamism,
每隔一段时间我就得做一些像硬装订一样的事情。
and every once in a while I have to do something like a hard binding.
然后我从这个系统中得到了很多好处，
Then I'm getting a lot of benefits out of that system,
似乎是一个合理的取舍。
seems like a reasonable trade-off.
另一方面，如果我不厌其烦地写出一个有意识的系统
On the other hand, if I go to all the trouble to write a this aware system and
然后每个人或者我的大部分呼叫站点都必须使用not bind，这对我来说是一条线索。
then everyone or most of my calls sites have to use not bind, that's a clue to me.
我在用艰难的方式做这件事。
I'm doing this the hard way.
我应该切换回并使用可预测的词法闭合。
I should switch back and use the predictable lexical closure.
换句话说，有更好的工具使用，有更好的方法来使用工具。
In other words, there's a better tool use, there's a better way to use the tool.
用它擅长的东西。
Use what it's good at.
如果我们想要灵活的动态性，使用this关键字，如果我们想要可预测性，
If we want flexible dynamism, use a this keyword, if we want predictability,
使用闭包，使用词法范围。
use closures, use lexical scope.
&gt；&gt；Kyle：所以在使用.bind方法时要记住这一点。
&gt;&gt; Kyle: So just keep that in mind when you're using the .bind method.
不是说它是坏的，不是说它是邪恶的，也不是说它是一种反模式。
Not that it is bad, not that it is evil, not that it is an anti-pattern.
但如果你发现这种情况经常发生
But if you find that happening more often than not,
你可能在用艰难的方式做事情。
you're probably doing things the hard way.